<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>software on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>example.com/tags/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in software on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="example.com/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Rescue Robot</title>
      <link>example.com/post/fire-rescue-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>example.com/post/fire-rescue-robot/</guid>
      <description>-- 
Sorry, your browser doesn&amp;rsquo;t support embedded videos, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you can download it and watch it with your favorite video player!  In Fall of 2017 I took the Mechanical Engineering Design and Methodology course, as a precursor to Senior Design the next semester. This course was structured to teach methods through hands-on design work for a project throughout the semester. The project for this semester was to create a fire rescue robot with the goal of entering a high-temperature environment and locating an injured pet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grafana Visualization</title>
      <link>example.com/post/grafana-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>example.com/post/grafana-visualization/</guid>
      <description>As part of the Student Cluster Competition team with TACC (details here), I created a power monitoring tool using graphite and grafana. During this time I realized how powerful a tool like grafana is for sharing and cleaning visualizing data and sought to find other applications for it. Recently I installed and configured both graphite and grafana to run on my local Raspberry Pi server. Currently this is used to display my network connectivity and system usage information, but I&amp;rsquo;m looking for other applications such as temperature logging, social media data analysis, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fluid Flow Simulation</title>
      <link>example.com/post/fluid-flow-simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>example.com/post/fluid-flow-simulation/</guid>
      <description>Solved velocity and pressure for flow through a 2 dimensional channel For the final project in my Parallel Programming class we were tasked with solving some problem using MPI on the HPC systems at Texas Advanced Computing Center (TACC). I was taking Fluid Mechanics at the same time, and chose to replicate one of the labs we had completed about the development of laminar flow. With the MPI C++ bindings, I wrote a basic simulation which depicted the flow of fluid through a two dimensional channel in the terms of pressure and velocity of the fluid elements in a mesh.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>